你觉得明天弄西岸主题之类的怎麽样？
What do you think a theme,
（太平洋西岸 左倾自由派地区）
like a West Coast feel for tomorrow?
我打算叫它“苗条的环太平洋”
I'm calling this "Pacific Trim."
你知道trim还有什麽意思？
You know what "trim" is?
什麽意思？
Yeah?
- B  - 哦 对
- It's twat. - Oh, yeah.
那麽女士 现在你在酒店
So, ma'am, right now, you're at your hotel.
我知道
I know that, yes.
“精彩Alcatraz”怎麽样？（西岸岛屿）
What about this "Alcatraz-matazz"?
你觉得怎麽样？
What do you think of that?
看起来像两个沙发
They look like two couches.
沙发啊 好极了 不能要沙发
Couches. Great. No couches.
明天早上去Clovis
Tomorrow morning is Clovis.
然后去Yahoo
Then you go to Yahoo.
记住 在那里不要用
Remember, while you're there,
Google当动词
do not use "Google" as a verb.
他们用Yahoo的
They "Yahoo" things there.
好了 再见
Okay, bye.
认识Meyer网势如破竹啊
"MeetMeyer.com" is burning down the house, ma'am,
如果那是好事的话
if that's a good thing.
这个水裂母女
What about this whole fracking
是什麽情况？
mother with this baby situation?